<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kbreakout.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Utbrytning</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKBreakOutxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KBreakOut</name>
  <summary>KBreakOut is a Breakout-like game by KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">El KBreakOut és un joc com el Breakout, creat per la comunitat KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KBreakOut és un joc com el Breakout, creat per la comunitat KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">KBreakOut ist ein Breakout-ähnliches Spiel von KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">KBreakOut is a Breakout-like game by KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">KBreakOut es un juego semejante a Breakout creado por KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">KBreakOut est un jeu de type Breakout par KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">KBreakOut é un xogo de rachar bloques de KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">KBreakOut adalah sebuah permainan seperti Breakout oleh KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">KBreakOut is een Breakout-achtig spel door KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">O KBreakOut é um jogo do tipo Breakout pelo KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">O KBreakOut é um jogo semelhante ao Breakout (quebra de barreiras) do KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Utbrytning är ett spel som liknar Breakout av KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">KBreakOut — це гра, схожа на Breakout, від KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxKBreakOut is a Breakout-like game by KDExx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      The objective of KBreakOut is to destroy as many bricks as possible without losing the ball.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'objectiu del KBreakOut és destruir tants maons com sigui possible sense perdre la pilota.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">L'objectiu del KBreakOut és destruir tants maons com siga possible sense perdre la pilota.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Das Ziel des Spiels ist es, so viele Steine wie möglich zu zerstören, ohne den Ball zu verlieren.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">The objective of KBreakOut is to destroy as many bricks as possible without losing the ball.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">El objetivo de KBreakOut es destruir tantos ladrillos como sea posible sin perder la bola.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">L'objectif de KBreakOut est de casser le plus de briques possibles sans faire tomber la balle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">O obxectivo de KBreakOut é destruír tantos bloques como for posíbel sen perder a bóla.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Sasaran KBreakOut adalah menghancurkan semua bata yang memungkinkan tanpa peluputan bola.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Het doel van KBreakOut is om zoveel mogelijk bakstenen te vernietigen zonder de bal te verliezen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O objectivo do KBreakOut é destruir tantos tijolos quantos possíveis, sem perder a bola.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O objetivo do KBreakOut é destruir o maior número possível de tijolos sem deixar a bola cair.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Syftet med Utbrytning är att förstöra så många tegelstenar som möjligt utan att förlora bollen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Метою гри є знищити якомога більше блоків без втрати кульки.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThe objective of KBreakOut is to destroy as many bricks as possible without losing the ball.xx</p>
    <p>
        The player is presented with a game field containing a number of bricks. A ball travels across the screen, bouncing off the top and side walls. When a brick is hit, the ball bounces away and the brick is destroyed. The player loses a life when the ball touches the bottom of the field. To prevent this from happening, the player has to use a movable bar to bounce the ball upward, situated at the bottom of the window. The purpose of the game is to progress through the levels destroying all bricks present in each, and trying to get a highscore.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El jugador té un camp que conté maons. Una pilota viatja per la pantalla, rebotant a la paret superior i a les laterals. Quan col·lideix amb un maó, la pilota rebota i el maó es destrueix. El jugador perd una vida quan la pilota toca la part inferior del camp. Per evitar-ho, el jugador té que usar una barra mòbil situada a la part inferior de la finestra per rebotar la pilota cap amunt. L'objectiu del joc és progressar pels nivells destruint tots els maons de cada nivell, intentant aconseguir una puntuació màxima.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El jugador té un camp que conté maons. Una pilota viatja per la pantalla, rebotant a la paret superior i a les laterals. Quan col·lideix amb un maó, la pilota rebota i el maó es destrueix. El jugador perd una vida quan la pilota toca la part inferior del camp. Per evitar-ho, el jugador té que usar una barra mòbil situada a la part inferior de la finestra per rebotar la pilota cap amunt. L'objectiu del joc és progressar pels nivells destruint tots els maons de cada nivell, intentant aconseguir una puntuació màxima.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Dem Spieler wird ein Spielfeld mit einer Anzahl an Steinen präsentiert. Ein Ball wandert über den Bildschirm, springt dabei aber von der oberen und den seitlichen Wänden ab. Wenn ein Stein getroffen wird, springt der Ball ab und der Stein ist zerstört. Der Spieler verliert ein Leben, wenn der Ball das untere Ende des Feldes berührt. Um das zu verhindern, muss der Spieler den Ball mithilfe einer beweglichen Leiste am unteren Rand zurückspringen lassen. Das Ziel des Spieles ist es, die Ebenen zu durchlaufen, indem alle Steine darin zerstört werden, und dabei noch einen hohen Punktestand zu erreichen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">The player is presented with a game field containing a number of bricks. A ball travels across the screen, bouncing off the top and side walls. When a brick is hit, the ball bounces away and the brick is destroyed. The player loses a life when the ball touches the bottom of the field. To prevent this from happening, the player has to use a movable bar to bounce the ball upward, situated at the bottom of the window. The purpose of the game is to progress through the levels destroying all bricks present in each, and trying to get a highscore.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Al jugador se le muestra un campo de juego que contiene cierto número de ladrillos. Una bola se desplaza por la pantalla, rebotando en las paredes de la parte superior y de los laterales. Al alcanzar un ladrillo, la bola rebota y el ladrillo se destruye. El jugador pierde una vida cada vez que la bola toca la parte inferior del campo. Para evitar que ocurra esto, el jugador debe usar una barra móvil situada en la parte inferior de la ventana para hacer que la bola rebote hacia arriba. El objetivo del juego consiste en progresar a través de varios niveles destruyendo todos los ladrillos presentes en cada uno de ellos para tratar de obtener una alta puntuación.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Le joueur fait face à un mur comprenant un certain nombre de briques. Une balle traverse l'écran en rebondissant sur les murs latéraux et supérieurs. Lorsqu'une brique est touchée, la balle rebondit et la brique est détruite. Le joueur perd une vie si la balle touche le bas de l'écran. Pour survivre, le joueur doit utiliser une barre qui se déplace latéralement en bas de la fenêtre et faire rebondir la balle. L'objectif du jeu est de progresser vers les niveaux supérieurs en détruisant la totalité des briques afin de se hisser au palmarès des meilleurs scores.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Ao xogador preséntaselle un campo de xogo que contén determinada cantidade de bloques. Unha bóla atravesa a pantalla, rebotando nas paredes superior e laterais. Cando bate nun bloque, a bóla rebota e o bloque é destruído. O xogador perde unha vida cando a bóla toca o fondo do campo. Para evitar que isto ocorra, o xogador ten que usar unha barra móbil para facer rebotar a bóla cara riba, situada no fondo da xanela. O obxectivo do xogo é avanzar polos niveis destruíndo todos os bloques que aparezan en cada un e intentando obter unha puntuación máxima.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Pemain disajikan dengan bidang permainan yang berisi sejumlah batu bata. Sebuah bola bergerak lalu-lalang melintasi layar, memantul dari atas dan samping dinding. Ketika batu bata terpukul bola yang memantul dan batu bata hancur. Pemain kehilangan hidup ketika bola menyentuh bagian bawah bidang. Untuk mencegah ini dari yang terjadi, pemain harus menggunakan bilah yang bisa digerakkan untuk memantulkan bola ke atas, terletak di bagian bawah window. Tujuan dari permainan ini adalah progres melalui level menghancurkan semua batu bata yang ada di tempat masing-masing, dan mencoba untuk mendapatkan skor tinggi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">De speler krijgt een speelveld te zien met daarin een aantal bakstenen. Een bal verplaatst zich over het scherm, stuiterend tegen de bovenkant en de muren aan de zijkanten. Als het een baksteen raakt dan stuitert de bal weg en is de baksteen vernietigd. De speler verliest een leven als de bal de onderkant van het veld raakt. Om dit te voorkomen moet de speler een beweegbare speelbalk gebruiken om de de bal weer omhoog te stuiteren, die onderaan het venster te vinden is. Het doel van het spel is door de levels te gaan ondertussen alle aanwezige bakstenen vernietigend en een hoge score te krijgen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">É apresentado ao jogador um campo de jogo que contém uma determinada quantidade de tijolos. Uma bola percorre o ecrã, fazendo ricochete nas paredes superior e laterais. Quando atingir um tijolo, a bola ressalta e o tijolo é destruído. O jogador perde uma vida quando a bola atingir o fundo do campo. Para evitar que isto aconteça, o jogador dispõe de uma barra móvel para ressaltar a bola para cima, situando-se esta barra no fundo da janela. O intuito do jogo é progredir pelos níveis, destruindo todos os tijolos presentes em cada um, tentando obter um recorde.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O jogador é presenteado com um campo de jogo contendo um número de tijolos. Uma bola viaja através da tela, batendo nas paredes superiores e laterais. Quando um tijolo é atingido, a bola é repelida e o tijolo é destruído. O jogador perde uma vida quando a bola toca o fundo do campo. Para evitar que isto aconteça, o jogador tem que usar uma barra móvel situada na parte inferior da tela para rebater a bola para cima. O objetivo do jogo é progredir através dos níveis destruindo todos os tijolos presentes em cada um, etentando obter um recorde.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Ett spelfält som innehåller ett antal tegelstenar visas för spelaren. En boll rör sig över skärmen, och studsar från väggarna längs överkanten och sidorna. När en tegelsten träffas, studsar bollen bort och tegelstenen förstörs. Spelaren förlorar ett liv när bollen rör vid fältets underkant. För att förhindra att det sker, måste spelaren använda en rörlig platta, som finns längst ner i fönstret, för att studsa bollen uppåt. Spelets syfte är att ta sig igenom alla nivåer, förstöra tegelstenarna som finns i varje nivå, och försöka uppnå bästa poäng.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Перед гравцем буде показано ігрове поле з декількома блоками. полем пересуватиметься кулька, яка відбиватиметься від бічних і верхньої стін. Якщо кулька влучить у блок, вона відіб’ється від нього, а сам блок буде зруйновано. Якщо кулька торкнеться нижньої стіни ігрового поля, гравець втратить одне життя. Щоб цього не сталося, гравцеві слід буде пересувати розташовану у нижній частині ігрового поля рисочку, якою можна відбивати кульку угору. Метою гри є просування рівнями шляхом руйнування всіх блоків на кожному з пройдених рівнів, а також збільшення очкового результату гри.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThe player is presented with a game field containing a number of bricks. A ball travels across the screen, bouncing off the top and side walls. When a brick is hit, the ball bounces away and the brick is destroyed. The player loses a life when the ball touches the bottom of the field. To prevent this from happening, the player has to use a movable bar to bounce the ball upward, situated at the bottom of the window. The purpose of the game is to progress through the levels destroying all bricks present in each, and trying to get a highscore.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://games.kde.org/game.php?game=kbreakout</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kbreakout</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kbreakout</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kbreakout&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Playing KBreakOut</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Jugant al KBreakOut</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Jugant al KBreakOut</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">KBreakOut spielen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Playing KBreakOut</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Jugando a KBreakOut</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Partie de KBreakOut en cours</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Xogando a KBreakOut</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Memainkan KBreakOut</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">KBreakOut spelen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Jogar ao KBreakOut</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Jogando KBreakOut</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Hranie KBreakOut</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Spela Utbrytning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Гра у KBreakOut</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxPlaying KBreakOutxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">KBreakOut 遊玩畫面</caption>
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kbreakout.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
</component>
