<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kbreakout.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KBreakOut</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKBreakOutxx</name>
  <summary>KBreakOut is a Breakout-like game by KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">El KBreakOut és un joc com el Breakout, creat per la comunitat KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">KBreakOut is een Breakout-achtig spel door KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">O KBreakOut é um jogo do tipo Breakout pelo KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">KBreakOut — це гра, схожа на Breakout, від KDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxKBreakOut is a Breakout-like game by KDExx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      The objective of KBreakOut is to destroy as many bricks as possible without losing the ball.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">L'objectiu del KBreakOut és destruir tants maons com sigui possible sense perdre la pilota.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Het doel van KBreakOut is om zoveel mogelijk bakstenen te vernietigen zonder de bal te verliezen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O objectivo do KBreakOut é destruir tantos tijolos quantos possíveis, sem perder a bola.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Метою гри є знищити якомога більше блоків без втрати кульки.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThe objective of KBreakOut is to destroy as many bricks as possible without losing the ball.xx</p>
    <p>
        The player is presented with a game field containing a number of bricks. A ball travels across the screen, bouncing off the top and side walls. When a brick is hit, the ball bounces away and the brick is destroyed. The player loses a life when the ball touches the bottom of the field. To prevent this from happening, the player has to use a movable bar to bounce the ball upward, situated at the bottom of the window. The purpose of the game is to progress through the levels destroying all bricks present in each, and trying to get a highscore.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El jugador té un camp que conté maons. Una pilota viatja per la pantalla, rebotant a la paret superior i a les laterals. Quan col·lisiona amb un maó, la pilota rebota i el maó es destrueix. El jugador perd una vida quan la pilota toca la part inferior del camp. Per evitar-ho, el jugador té que usar una barra mòbil situada a la part inferior de la finestra per rebotar la pilota cap amunt. L'objectiu del joc és progressar pels nivells destruint tots els maons de cada nivell, intentant aconseguir una puntuació màxima.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">De speler krijgt een speelveld te zien met daarin een aantal bakstenen. Een bal verplaatst zich over het scherm, stuiterend tegen de bovenkant en de muren aan de zijkanten. Als het een baksteen raakt dan stuitert de bal weg en is de baksteen vernietigd. De speler verliest een leven als de bal de onderkant van het veld raakt. Om dit te voorkomen moet de speler een beweegbare speelbalk gebruiken om de de bal weer omhoog te stuiteren, die onderaan het venster te vinden is. Het doel van het spel is door de levels te gaan ondertussen alle aanwezige bakstenen vernietigend en een hoge score te krijgen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">É apresentado ao jogador um campo de jogo que contém uma determinada quantidade de tijolos. Uma bola percorre o ecrã, fazendo ricochete nas paredes superior e laterais. Quando atingir um tijolo, a bola ressalta e o tijolo é destruído. O jogador perde uma vida quando a bola atingir o fundo do campo. Para evitar que isto aconteça, o jogador dispõe de uma barra móvel para ressaltar a bola para cima, situando-se esta barra no fundo da janela. O intuito do jogo é progredir pelos níveis, destruindo todos os tijolos presentes em cada um, tentando obter um recorde.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Перед гравцем буде показано ігрове поле з декількома блоками. полем пересуватиметься кулька, яка відбиватиметься від бічних і верхньої стін. Якщо кулька влучить у блок, вона відіб’ється від нього, а сам блок буде зруйновано. Якщо кулька торкнеться нижньої стіни ігрового поля, гравець втратить одне життя. Щоб цього не сталося, гравцеві слід буде пересувати розташовану у нижній частині ігрового поля рисочку, якою можна відбивати кульку угору. Метою гри є просування рівнями шляхом руйнування всіх блоків на кожному з пройдених рівнів, а також збільшення очкового результату гри.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThe player is presented with a game field containing a number of bricks. A ball travels across the screen, bouncing off the top and side walls. When a brick is hit, the ball bounces away and the brick is destroyed. The player loses a life when the ball touches the bottom of the field. To prevent this from happening, the player has to use a movable bar to bounce the ball upward, situated at the bottom of the window. The purpose of the game is to progress through the levels destroying all bricks present in each, and trying to get a highscore.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">http://games.kde.org/game.php?game=kbreakout</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kbreakout</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kbreakout</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=kbreakout&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Playing KBreakOut</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Jugant al KBreakOut</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">KBreakOut spelen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Jogar ao KBreakOut</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Гра у KBreakOut</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxPlaying KBreakOutxx</caption>
      <image>http://kde.org/images/screenshots/kbreakout.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
</component>
